// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question:
      "There are 2 positive integers x and y. What is the probability that x + y is odd?",
    answer: "1/2",
    options: ["1/2", "3/2", "2/5", "8/3"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question:
      "What is the harmonic mean of two numbers whose geometric mean and arithmetic mean are 6 and 12, respectively?",
    answer: "3",
    options: ["5", "3", "8", "1"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "If GM = 12 and HM = 7.2, then what will be the value of AM?",
    answer: "20",
    options: ["22", "18", "34", "16"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the sum of all the odd numbers up to 100?",
    answer: "2500",
    options: ["2200", "2100", "1800", "2500"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the maximum sum of the series 60, 56, 52, 48, ...?",
    answer: "480",
    options: ["500", "513", "699", "480"],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question:
      "Three year ago, ratio of Tom and Ram age’s was 5 : 6 respectively. After 12 years, this ratio becomes 6 : 7. How old is Ram at present?",
    answer: "93",
    options: ["87", "98", "93", "73"],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question:
      "Ratio of ages of three girls are 5:8:10, six years ago, the sum of their ages was 28. Find their present ages.",
    answer: "10,16,20",
    options: ["10,16,20", "23,52,11", "75,86,13", "None"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question:
      "Shyam is younger than Sharuk by 22 years. If the ratio of their ages is 5:7, find the age of Shyam",
    answer: "55",
    options: ["100", "23", "55", "73"],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question:
      "The ratio between the present ages of M and N is 8:9. If N is 6 years old than M, what will be the ratio of the ages of M and N after 6 years",
    answer: "Structured Query Language",
    options: ["9:10", "9:6", "9:11", "9:12"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question:
      "Ratio between vinodha and swetha is 7:6, After 8 Years vinodha’s age will be 29 years. What is swetha present age.",
    answer: "18",
    options: ["15", "12", "13", "18"],
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  // {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "option 3",
  //   options: ["Option 1", "option 2", "option 3", "option 4"],
  // },
];
